names.co.uk 2012-06-19

# Privacy Statement - Namesco

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

### GENERAL

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Namesco Limited in relation to this Namesco website (the "Website"):

"we", "us" and "our" refer collectively to Namesco Limited ("Namesco") (Company number 03913408) having its registered office at Acton House, Perdiswell Park, Worcester, WR3 7GD and its Group Companies (from time to time). "Group Companies" means Namesco, its Holding Companies, its Subsidiaries and the Subsidiaries of any of its Holding Companies from time to time ("Holding Company" and "Subsidiary" having the meanings set out in section 1159 Companies Act 2006). Namesco Limited is part of the Dada group of companies.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is intended to give you confidence in the privacy and security of the personal information we obtain from you whether you upload information to this Website, download it, or are merely visiting. 

Please note that we are not responsible for any use of your personal information you provide to third party websites that may be accessed via this Website. You will therefore need to review the privacy policy of any third party websites that you use.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you use this Website you may be asked for personally identifiable information such as your name, address, date of birth, email address and telephone number. You may also be asked for financial information for billing and payment purposes. By giving us such information you agree to our using it in the manner described in this policy. 

You may withdraw your consent to our use of your personal information for this purpose at any time by emailing us at support@names.co.uk and we will aim to process this request within 5 days of receipt of your withdrawal of consent.

Cookie information, pages you have requested and your IP address may also be recorded by us from your browser as set out in this Privacy Policy.

### OUR CAPACITY AS DATA PROCESSOR

As part of the services we provide to you, we may host and store the personal data of your customers (for example through our provision of web hosting, e-mail transmission and data storage services to you). This is done in our capacity as a data processor and we are not ultimately in control of what happens to this data. Our processing of such personal data will be in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and any agreement with the relevant data processor.

### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may use your information to process your service requests, provide access to secure areas of the Website, to personalise your visit to the Website and to enable us to review, develop and continually improve the services we provide online. We also use this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

If you do not wish to continue to receive such information from Namesco and its Group Companies or third parties, please e-mail support@names.co.uk or alternatively when we send you an e-mail, follow the instructions at the end of the message explaining how you can opt-out of receiving any further information from us.

### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Any disclosure of personal information will be strictly controlled and made fully in accordance with current UK legislation, in particular the UK Data Protection Act 1998. 

We may provide information about you to third parties, our employees and agents in order to administer any accounts and services provided to you by Namesco and its Group Companies. Any access to or use by third parties of personal information provided by you will only be to perform functions on our behalf related to purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and may not be used for any other purpose.

Should you breach our terms and conditions or any Website terms of use or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, we may disclose your information to a relevant authority. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We may share aggregated statistical demographic information about you with our partners and advertisers. This information is anonymised.

You agree that we may disclose your personal information to third parties in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets and their advisers. Any disclosure of personal information will be strictly controlled and made fully in accordance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003.

### TRANSFER OF YOUR DATA OUTSIDE OF THE EEA

As part of the services offered to you through this Website, the information you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside of the European Economic Area ("EEA"). These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA. If we transfer your information outside of the EEA in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

### RIGHT TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. You can obtain access to your personal information held by us by sending a cheque for £10 (to cover administration costs for collating this information), made payable to "Namesco", to: Data Protection Officer, Acton House, Perdiswell Park, Worcester, Worcs WR3 7GD. If you have any questions about Namesco’s Data Protection Policy please write to our Data Protection Officer or e-mail us at support@names.co.uk. We may ask you to give evidence of your identity before providing such access.

We always endeavour to make sure that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date, if you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or e-mail us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### COOKIES AND LOG FILES

We may create and access cookies (a piece of information which is stored on your computer and allows us to identify if you have visited the site before) on your PC. Cookies cannot be executed as code or used to deliver a virus. Other servers cannot read them and personal information cannot be gathered from them. They are simply an identifier shared between you and us to allow us to improve the services we offer to you through our Website. 

If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your PC, then they can be disabled in your web browser. The option to do so is normally found in your browser's "security settings" section. However, please note, permanently disabling cookies in your browser may hinder your use of our Website as well as other websites and interactive services.

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the Website and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### SECURITY

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounting staff or a customer care representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

If you have any further concerns about security, please email our Customer Service team at suport@names.co.uk.

### E-MAIL

Wherever possible, Namesco and its Group Companies sets security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data. However any information and personal data carried over the Internet and by e-mail is not secure and is liable to interception, loss, redirection and corruption by other people unless it is encrypted by you. 

### OPT – OUT

If you use this Website to purchase services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners you may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, or by contacting us directly.

### POLICY CHANGES

Changes in this policy will be posted on our Website. You are advised to check our Website regularly to view our most recent Privacy Policy.

*Get a .uk (co.uk, .me.uk, .org.uk) domain name with a 1 year registration, FREE with any of our Annual Web Hosting, SiteMaker or Ecommerce Packages.

‡ 4 Months Free Web Hosting applies to Professional, Premium and Platinum Annual and Multi-Year Hosting and is applied by giving 1/3 off the original annual price. Discount applies to new purchases and for the first billing period only. Offer cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer and may be withdrawn at any time at the discretion of Namesco. Standard terms and conditions of service apply.

**The 99p price for .EU domains excludes VAT (£1.18 incl. VAT) and is for initial billing period only. Standard renewal rate applies. Offers may be withdrawn at any time at the discretion of Namesco. Standard terms and conditions of service apply.

#### Dada Group Figures and Stats

  * 1,800,000 domains registered in over 250 extensions
  * 40,000 new registrations per month
  * 500,000 websites hosted on our platforms
  * 490,000 clients are using our products
